[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which condition is described as an excessive fear of animals?", "correct_answer": "Zoophobia", "incorrect_answers": ["Ailurophobia", "None of these", "Thalassophobia"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Born Charles Dennis Buchinsky in 1921, this The Dirty Dozen and Rider on the Rain actor was known in Italy as Il Brutto (The Ugly One).", "correct_answer": "Charles Bronson", "incorrect_answers": ["Ernest Borgnine", "Telly Savalas", "Donald Pleasence"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Belonephobia is the irrational fear of needles.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What US college football team plays on blue grass?", "correct_answer": "Boise State", "incorrect_answers": ["Kentucky", "Louisville", "Utah State"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Does Mercury have a magnetic field?", "correct_answer": "Yes", "incorrect_answers": ["No"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In 2007 the amount of cheetahs left in the wild dropped to what number?", "correct_answer": "12,000", "incorrect_answers": ["20,000", "30,000", "5,000"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In Sin City, Jackie Boy shoots himself.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What causes Indys scar above his chin in the movie The Last Crusade?", "correct_answer": "A Whip", "incorrect_answers": ["A Snake", "A Lion", "A Knife"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This US city is located at the confluence of the Mississippi River and the Ohio River.", "correct_answer": "Cairo, Illinois", "incorrect_answers": ["Pittsburgh, Pennsylvania", "Chicago, Illinois", "Memphis, Tennessee"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the major type of food that Hummingbirds depend on for their survival?", "correct_answer": "Nectar", "incorrect_answers": ["All of these", "Seeds", "Buds"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the common name for the pigeon that we see in the city streets and in our backyards?", "correct_answer": "Rock Dove", "incorrect_answers": ["Mourning Dove", "Common Dove", "Fancy Dove"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The Humpback Whale, one of the largest marine mammals, feeds in this season.", "correct_answer": "Summer", "incorrect_answers": ["Spring and winter", "Winter", "Fall"]}]